Everyone
다
Hi
안녕
Hi Flover testing Ai generate subs, please disable if uncomfortable. warning is removed at 0:15
안녕 플라버
They're not here yet
아직 안 오
Oh
오
They're coming in
들어왔다
Oh my
이걸 오야
Whose account did you turn this on with I turned it on with mine
이거 누구 거로 켰어 내 거 내 걸로켰어
Yeah what do we do if you turn it on with your account Unnie
응 언니걸로 켜면 어떡해
But if we turn it on with Hanyang's account
근데 이거 하나 걸로 켜면
as a group ah then should we switch
단체로 아 그럼 바꿀까
Unnie can only one person see that
언니 그거 한 사람만 볼 수 있나
Ah
아,
can't everyone see it everyone can't see it
다 볼 수 있지 않아? 다 못 봐.
No they can't
아니야. 못 봐.
Then we can turn it on as a group too
그럼 단체로도 켤 수 있.
Then should we all turn it on as a group
그러면은 단체로 다 켜볼까?
Then we do that and
그러면하고
You should have organized things before turning it on
아니 정리를 하고 켜던지
Why are you turning it on first and then organizing
앞에 왜 켜서 정리를 하냐고?
Ah wait a minute no this is
아, 잠깐만. 아니, 이게
Is this only visible to people who subscribed to Hanyang
이게 한양을 구독한 사람만 볼 수있는 거야?
Right
맞아.
But last time for my birthday live Is this only visible to people who subscribed to Hanyang
근데 나 저번에 생일라이
I did it But last time for my birthday live
했어요.
Everyone could see it I did it
다 볼 수 있었어요.
But group setting
근데 단체로 설정
wasn't turned on
켜지 않았어.
Ah then let's ask the company
아, 그럼 회사에 물어보자. [웃음]
Then but why didn't everyone subscribe
그러면 근데 왜 다 구독을 안 했어?
That's so sad
너무 서운하나 [환호]
Then should we take this one from here
그럼 우리 여기서는 여기 뺏어볼까?
Yeah
그러네.
Whose is this
이거 누구 타지?
Nothing went up oh my then unnie turn this on for the group
안 올라갔어. 아무것도 헐. 그러면이거 단체로 언니가 먹혀
once ah we set this up once before
한번. 아 이거 저번에 설정 한번 한적이 있는데
Uh unnie
어 언니가
No but I have the power here
아니 내가 근데 권력자다잉.
Not that but the company
그게 아니라 회사에서
did it for us
해줬어.
Ah then we can't turn this on
아 그럼 이건 우리가 못 켜
Just simultaneously I'm curious
그냥 동시 나 궁금하겠네. 내
Should we try doing it simultaneously
동시 한번 해 볼래?
Marketing
마케팅.
Ah I'll try contacting them right now uh Should we try doing it simultaneously
아 내가 지금 저 연락해 볼게. 어
Marketing ah don't do it just turn them on simultaneously Ah I'll try contacting them right now uh
마케팅 아 하지 마. 동시에 키워.
Ah we can't do lives simultaneously Marketing ah don't do it just turn them on simultaneously
아 라이브가 동시에 안 돼.
Ah really ah this is too much Ah we can't do lives simultaneously
아그래. 아 이거 너무하다.
Why is it good
왜 좋은 거지?
Why we could make fun content by turning them on simultaneously
왜 동시에 켜서 재밌는 컨텐츠를 만들수도 있잖아.
It's dark
어두워.
Yeah Why we could make fun content by turning them on simultaneously
응.
Uh
어.
Yeah isn't it better to just have one on
응. 이게 하나 켜는게 나 있는게낫지 않아?
I know it's dark
그니까 어두워.
Here
여기가
We can't help it here
그거 어쩔 수 없긴 여기
itself is a bit uh
자체가 좀 어
Ah for now should we turn this off for a second then
아 일단 [목을 가다듬음] 우리 이거잠깐만 끌까? 그러면
Why who's coming then
왜 어디 와? 그러면은
I'll go ask if we can turn it on as a group I'm getting dizzy
단체로 캘 수있는지 물어보고 올게요.어질어질하다.